# Vrinda Goel

#### **Software Developer**

Junior year college student with over 5 years of experience in coding. Interned as a Software Developer in an Artificial Intelligence platform based company and also gained experience in debugging, testing and problem solving as a Teaching Assistant in various labs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Teaching Assistant - Database Management Systems Lab

LNM IIT, August 2018 - PRESENT

### Summer Intern - Software Development

Razorthink Inc., June 2018 - July 2018

### Teaching Assistant - C Programming Lab

LNM IIT, August 2017 - December 2017

#### **EDUCATION**

## **LNM IIT,** Jaipur — Bachelors in Science, Computer Science

August 2016 - May 2020 CGPA(After 4th Semester) on a scale of 10(only CSE courses) : 9.39 CGPA(After 4th Semester) on a scale of 10 : 8.20

# National Public School RNR, Bangalore — High School

June 2004 - March 2016 Secondary Boards : 10 CGPA. Senior Secondary Boards : 92.6%.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### 2013

High distinction in Computer Science and Distinction in Maths in the International Assessment for Indian Schools (IAIS).

#### 2015

Distinction in Maths and Computer Science in the International Assessment for Indian Schools (IAIS).

#### 2016

Ranked 1st in batch and 14th in college in the Inter university Programming Competition. Have been ranked in the top 30 in various other coding competitions in college.

#### 2017

Ranked 9th out of 70 teams that participated in the online round of The LNMIIT CodeSprint and 4th out of the 34 teams that qualified for the on-site round held on Codeforces

#### **INTERESTS**

I am a psychology and travel aficionado, write and also play the keyboard.

#### Phone

(+91)80038-90410

#### **Email**

vrinda.keepsmiling@gmail.com

#### Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vrinda41198/

#### GitHub

https://github.com/vrinda41198/

#### **SKILLS**

**Languages**: C++, C, Java(moderate)

**Scripting**: Python **DBMS**: MySQL, DB2

Environments: Vim, Eclipse,

OMNet++, PyCharm.

#### **LEADERSHIP POSITIONS**

#### 2017 - 2018

Women-in Tech Evangelist

#### 2017 - 2018

Core Organising Committee Member

#### **2018 - PRESENT**

Associate General Secretary, The Science and Technical Council

#### **PROIECTS**

#### Brick Game: C++

Made an ASCII game based on the racing brick\_game with added features.

### Movie ticket booking portal : C++

Inspired by the BookmyShow website.

Intelligent Document Processor: Python, Regex, JSON, Neo4j

N - Queens Problem : Python, Genetic Algorithms